Logitech Privacy Policy | How We Protect Your Information
=========================================================

Our Brands

Free standard shipping on orders over $29.00

1. Delayed Shipping Meg
2. Express Delivery
3. Free Shipping
4. Ukraine promo
5. Carbon Neutral
6. Summer Sale

* Shop
    
    Shop Close
    
    *  Shop
        
        ---------------------------------------------------------

        Mice

        -----------------------------------------------------------------------------

        KEYBOARDS & CONSOLE

        Webcams & Audio
        ---------------

        Webcams & Audio

        Mobile Solutions
        ----------------

        Mobile Solutions

        New & Featured
        --------------

        New & Featured

        ------------------------------------------------------------

        For Business

        --------------------------------------------------------------

        For Education

        ---------------------------------------------

        For Gaming

        Shop our series
        ---------------

        Shop our series

* Deals
    
    Deals Close
    
        -----------------------------------------------------------

        Current Offers

        ---------------------------------------------------------------------

        Gifts with Purchase

        -----------------------------------------------------------------------

        Save with Combos

        --------------------------------------------------------------------------------

        Refurbished Products

* Discover
    
    Discover Close
    
        --------------------------------------------------------------------

        Sustainability

        -----------------------------------------------------

        About Us

        -------------------------------------------------------------------

        Ergo Series

        -----------------------------------------------------------------

        MX Series

        * [**Designed with sustainability in mind. See our pledge** See our sustainability pledge](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/sustainability.html)

* Business
    
    Business Close
    
        ----------------------------------------------------------------------------

        Spaces & Solutions

        -----------------------------------------------------------------

        Products

        -----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

        Software & Services

        Partners
        --------

        Partners

        -------------------------------------------------------------------------
        
        Resources

* Support
    
    Support Close
    
    * For Individuals
        ---------------

        For Individuals

        For Business & Education
        ------------------------

        For Business & Education

        -------------------------------------------------------------
        
        Software

Search... Search [My Account](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/my-account.html)[](https://www.logitech.com/bin/cart/view)

SUBMIT

Pangea temporary hotfixes here

Logitech Privacy Policy
-----------------------

**Last updated:** September 2024

Your privacy is essential to Logitech. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle your personal data.

Logitech's previous Product Privacy Policy and Web Privacy Policy have been combined into this one comprehensive Privacy Policy to provide you with a unified and clear explanation on how we process your personal data. The previous Product Privacy Policy can be viewed [here](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/legal/product-privacy-policy/product-privacy-policy-archive.html) and the previous Website Privacy Policy [here](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/legal/web-privacy-policy/web-privacy-policy-archive.html).

This Privacy Policy is applicable to all data we handle through our products and services, our websites and mobile sites (Sites), our applications (apps), software and other devices. Logitech operates under its parent company, Logitech Europe S.A., and the specific Logitech company that controls your data may vary depending on your relationship with us (whether it be as a customer, partner, supplier, contractor or any other relevant relationship).

General
-------

The sections below detail the types of personal data we collect, how we use them, and how we protect personal data collected through our products, services, websites, apps, software and other devices.

Our Products
------------

The sections below detail the specific personal data we collect for the products and services listed, how we use the personal data collected and the options you have to control your information and preferences.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT
----------------------

We may collect data in a variety of ways to improve our products and services, including through your interactions with our products, website and services, as well as to deliver personalized advertising and communications based on your interests:

* **Information you provide to us**  
    This includes information you provide when you register and set up new products, download software, post on online platforms like forums or communities, respond to a survey, or enter a contest.
* **Information from the use of products and services**  
    When you use certain products and services, data may be sent to us to help improve your experience and troubleshoot issues. This may include details about your device such as hardware model, firmware and operating system version, unique device identifiers, and online identifiers like your IP address. In some cases, if you’ve enabled location services on your device and in the app settings, we may also collect general location information to provide relevant features or support. Other times, subject to applicable law and your consent where it is required, we may collect data based on your activities including your settings and configurations, usage data, and crash or error data.

We may also collect and otherwise process business contact information that you provide to us, or that we collect from your organization, such as our business partners and suppliers when we are doing business and in the context of performing an agreement. Where notice or consent is required for such processing, the organization will notify and obtain such consent from its respective personnel and authorized users.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

The data we receive depends on the products, services and features you use, events in which you may participate, business engagements and other interactions you may have with us. This data can include the following:

* **Name and contact data** – data like your name, personal or business email address, personal or business postal address, personal or business phone number, user ID and other similar contact data.
* **Credentials** – passwords, hints, and information used for authentication and account access.
* **Demographic data** – data like your age, gender, country, and preferred language.
* **Payment data** – data needed to process your order if you make purchases through a Logitech website, like your shipping address, products ordered, and contact information. When you buy digital products we process payment data such as the value of transaction, what subscriptions you purchased and, if applicable, your Paypal, WeChat, AliPay or Stripe ID. We do not collect payment or credit card numbers.
* **Usage data** – data about how you and your device interact with us and our products, like:
    * **product usage data** – the features you use, actions you take, and activities you perform, like button customization preferences, interactions with an app, or time spent listening to a speaker;
    * **device data** – data about your device and the network you use to connect to our products, including the operating systems and other software on your device, device identifiers, and regional and language settings;
    * **other product data** – information from other devices and software, like stereo, home automation, and television product information, cable provider information;
    * **error reports and performance data** – the type or severity of the problem, details of the software or hardware related to an error, the contents of files you were using when an error occurred, and data about other software on your device; and
    * **support data** – information about you and your hardware, software, and details about the event, authentication data, your communications with us, data about the machine and the application you were using, and system, registry, and configuration data.
* **Interests and favorites** – your music preferences, programmed activities or routines, channels and radio stations, and services you use.
* **Contacts and relationships** – contacts and relationships if you use a product or service that supports multi-user, community and sharing functionality.
* **Logitech Accounts (Guest and Logi ID)** – there are different options available to create an account, depending on the product or service and your choice. You may decide not to create an account, but provide details as a guest. In this case, we may only collect limited information, such as your name, email address and shipping address. You may decide to create a personal Logitech account called Logi ID. In this case, we may also collect information such as your name, email address and telephone number and it will optimize your experience. For example, it may enable improved personalization and allow you to save and recall settings, configurations and history. We will assign a unique ID number to your account and information. When you sign into your account, we may collect information about your session, including a record of your sign-in, date and time, the product you signed into, the number assigned to your account, and a unique identifier assigned to your device, your IP address, your operating system and browser version. In general, when you sign into your account, you will stay signed in until you sign out.
* **Social Logins** – When you use a third party service such as Apple, Facebook, Google or Twitch to log in, we process the personal data that you have agreed to share via the third party platform in question. Please review the privacy notices presented to you by these third party services when linking your accounts for details on the information Logitech receives.
* **Location data** – Some products use location data for purposes like time/date and language preferences or for the purpose of legal compliance. Data we may collect about your location can be either precise or imprecise. Precise location data can be your home or work address information or Global Positioning System (GPS) data, which we may collect when you enable location-based products or features. Imprecise location data may include a location derived from your Wi-Fi or IP address or data that indicates where you are located with less precision, like a city or region.
* **Content** – We may collect information about the content of your files and communications when necessary to provide you with the products you use. We also may collect the content of messages you send to us, like feedback and product reviews you write, or questions and information you provide for customer support. We may contact you to understand your satisfaction with a product or service. When you contact us, phone conversations or chat sessions with representatives may be monitored and recorded subject to applicable law and your consent where it is required.

Participant data
----------------

We process your personal data when you sign up to become a participant in a Logitech:

* Beta Test;
* Interview;
* Research; or
* Survey

We use this personal data to invite you to become a participant and we use your feedback to develop and improve our products and services.

### 

Read more

### 

Read more

Read more

Examples of the information we receive and process include:

* your name, email address and phone number;
* the categories of products and services you are interested in;
* information in your product tester application;
* your testing activity, product data, service data, device data, and diagnostic data;
* video and/or audio recordings if they were part of the Beta Test, Interview, Research or Survey you participated in;
* shipment/fulfillment data to send you a Beta product;
* your feedback, review and comments during the Beta Test about the tested products and services, and questions asked during the Interview, Research or Survey.

Unless otherwise communicated to you when you sign up for our testing program, we process this data for the purpose of entering into or performing the contract between you and Logitech. With your consent, we may contact you for future similar Beta Test, Interviews, Research and Survey activities.

HOW WE USE INFORMATION
----------------------

We use the data we collect from our products and services:

1. to operate our business and provide, improve, and personalize our products and services, and
2. to send communications, including promotions, account information, security updates, and product information.

We may analyze this data, including your personal information, to give you a more seamless, consistent and personalized experience. We will always do so subject to applicable law and your consent where it’s required.

### 

Read more

### 

Read more

Read more

In addition, we use the data we collect from our Sites to provide you with rich, interactive experiences. In particular, we may use data from our websites to:

* provide the service or carry out the transactions at your request;
* improve and develop our products;
* personalize your experience;
* process job applications you submit through our Sites;
* advertise and market to you based on your consent or our legitimate interests, subject to applicable legal requirements, which may include sending promotional communications, targeted advertising, and presenting you with relevant offers via email, SMS, push notifications and personalized website experiences.

### 

Read more

### 

Read more

Read more

We do not sell your personal data.

We may share your personal data with third parties including advertising partners under certain circumstances for the Promotions and Relevant News function as listed in the table below. We use affiliated and unaffiliated service providers that help us process personal data to deliver services and run our business subject to strict confidentiality agreements. For example, service providers help deliver the following functions:

| **Service Description** | **Data Provided** | **Purpose** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Customer Support | Contact data, Inquiry data | To help troubleshoot and support products and services |
| E-Commerce Functionality | Contact data, Interactions with our Sites | To facilitate sales of our products online |
| Promotions and Relevant News | Contact data, Cookie data | To provide information and incentives for our products and services |
| Website performance | Cookie data, Interactions with our Sites | To enable functionality and features while on our websites |
| Cookie Manager | Cookie data | To provide the ability to choose which cookies are used on our Sites |

These companies are required to abide by our data protection and security requirements and are not allowed to use personal data they receive from us for any other purpose.

We may disclose your personal data to

1. comply with relevant laws, regulatory requirements, and to respond to lawful requests, including to meet national security requirements, court orders, and legal process;
2. to protect and defend our rights or property or that of third parties, including enforcing agreements, policies, and terms of use;
3. in an emergency, including to protect the safety of our employees or any person; or
4. in connection with investigating or preventing fraud.

We may share your personal data for purposes of a business deal, or negotiation of a business deal, involving the sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets. These deals can include any merger, financing, acquisition, divestiture, joint venture or partnership, or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding.

We also use and share aggregated and pseudonymous information for performance, analytics, and social network marketing purposes. This data is processed in a way that is not designed to identify you individually.

Providing and improving our products and services
-------------------------------------------------

We use data to provide and improve our products and services and to perform essential operations. This includes operating and using the products, maintaining and improving their performance, and using data to research, develop new features and provide customer support. Example uses include:

* **Providing the Product or Service**  
    We use data to ensure our products operate as intended and expected. Our products and services may have personalized features and recommendations that enhance your productivity and enjoyment, and tailor your experiences based on your activities, interests, and location.
* **Customer Satisfaction**  
    We use data to understand your satisfaction with the product or service.
* **Customer Support**  
    We use data to diagnose product problems, repair customers' devices, and provide other customer care and support services.
* **Product Activation and Registration**  
    We use device and application version, location, and unique device, network and identifiers and other data to activate and register products.
* **Product Improvement**  
    We use data to improve our products, add new features or capabilities, report errors, improve security, determine what new features to prioritize, and improve efficiency.
* **Security, Safety and Dispute Resolution**  
    We use data to protect the security and safety of our products and our users, to detect and prevent fraud, and to resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. For example, we may use data to determine which products need security patches or analyze patterns in data that allow us to develop new security features.
* **Business Operations**  
    We may use pseudonymous and aggregated data to create statistics and analysis. For example, financial and product reports are created to analyze performance in a given sector or region.
* **Marketing Communications**  
    We may use your personal information to send you marketing communications, or to engage with you in marketing activities, if you have opted-in or when we have a legitimate interest under applicable law to do so. These communications and activities occur in various ways and may be tailored to your interests based on your previous interactions with Logitech, including your purchase history and website engagement.

Below, you'll find an explanation of these activities, the categories of personal data involved, and the legal bases for processing.

| Description | Categories of Personal Data | Legal Basis for Processing |
| --- | --- | --- |
| We may send you emails about new products, services, exclusive promotions, surveys, and other promotional activities | Contact Data, Account Data | Consent |
| We may send you targeted surveys to understand your interests and preferences better. This helps us tailor product recommendations and offers to your specific needs | Contact Data, Account Data, Purchase Information, Website Browsing Data | Consent |
| We may use your information to provide you with personalized recommendations for products, content, educational articles and offers that we believe you may find relevant and interesting | Contact Data, Account Data, Purchase Information, Website Browsing Data | Consent |
| Based on your recent purchases, we may suggest complementary products that enhance your Logitech experience | Contact Data, Account Data, Purchase Information, Website Browsing Data | Consent |
| We may process aggregated data from the past two years to generate insights to improve our products and services and to honor your marketing opt-out preferences | Contact Data, Account Data, Purchase Information, Website Browsing Data, Aggregated Data | Legitimate Interest |

Your Choices:
-------------

* You can opt out of receiving marketing emails at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in the email; by visiting our [Preference Center](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/my-account/email-preferences.html); or by logging into your Logitech account and navigating to [Email Preferences](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/my-account/email-preferences.html).
* You can adjust your preferences for personalized recommendations and advertising in your account settings.
* Subject to applicable law and your consent where it's required, we may also use cookies or tracking technology to personalize your experience on our website and in our marketing communications. You can learn more about how we use cookies and tracking technologies in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/legal/cookie-policy.html).

**Support Communications**  
We may contact you by email or other means to inform you when a subscription is ending or to let you know when security updates are available.

**Cookies**  
Logitech uses cookies that are essentially small data files placed on your computer, tablet, mobile phone, or other devices. You can learn more about cookies, withdraw your consent or modify your choices at any time by clicking on the Cookie Settings button located at the bottom of our website.

SHARING AND DISCLOSING INFORMATION
----------------------------------

We do not sell your personal data.

We may share your personal data with your consent or to complete a transaction or provide a product or service you requested or authorized. We also share personal data among our controlled affiliates and subsidiaries for the purposes described in this policy and when required by law.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

We may share personal data with vendors or agents working on our behalf for the purposes described in this Policy. For example, companies hired to provide customer service support or assist in protecting and securing our systems and services may need access to personal data to provide those functions.

These companies must abide by our data protection and security requirements and are not allowed to use personal data they receive from us for any other purpose. We may also disclose personal data to another company if we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business. This may include any organization involved in a merger, transfer, or sale of our assets or business.

If you post information in public areas in our products and services, like communities, forums, or blogs, it will be available to the public and we may reuse and republish it at our discretion and in line with our Terms of Use.

Finally, we will access, transfer, disclose, and preserve personal data, including your content, when we have a good faith belief that doing so is necessary to:

1. comply with law or respond to a legal process, like national security requirements, law enforcement or other government agencies;
2. protect our customers, for example, to prevent spam or attempts to defraud our users, or to help prevent loss of life or serious injury;
3. maintain the security of our products, including to prevent or stop an attack on our systems or networks; and
4. protect your or our legal rights or as required by law or orders from a court or government agency.

**Information provided by you to third parties**  
We are not responsible for information provided by you to third parties, and that information is not subject to this policy. You assume all privacy, security, and other risks with providing information, including personal data, to third parties. To understand the privacy protections from third parties, you should refer to their privacy policies, if any.

CONTROLLING AND ACCESSING INFORMATION
-------------------------------------

You can direct us to update, delete, or deactivate certain information pertaining to you. You can also request that we remove your personal data from the blog, community forums, or other public areas within our control. If we cannot remove certain personal data, we will let you know why.

You also have the right to request how your data is processed and with whom we share it. Additionally, if you believe certain information Logitech processes about you is inaccurate, you have the right to have this information corrected. We will endeavor to respond to your request to review the information we have on file for you within 30 days from receiving such request.

You can unsubscribe from marketing emails from us by following the instructions in the email you received or at the [subscription management page](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/my-account/email-preferences.html) on our website. We try to respond to requests to review information we have on file within 30 days of receiving a request.

You can “opt-out” of having your personal data used for certain purposes whenever we ask for this information. If you have questions, comments or would like to make a request about your data or our Privacy Policy or data practices, please contact us at [support.logitech.com/response-center](https://support.logitech.com/response-center) or through the following methods:

Phone: +1 646-454-3200 or toll free +1 866 632 5644  
Contact: [support.logitech.com/response-center](https://support.logitech.com/response-center)

If you are not satisfied with our response, you can refer your privacy complaint or dispute to the state or national data protection authority in your jurisdiction.

CHILDREN
--------

We do not knowingly collect or maintain information about persons under 13 years of age. If we learn that information about persons under 13 years of age has been collected on or through Logitech sites, we will take appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 years of age who has registered for an account or service on our sites, please contact us using the contact information below to have that child’s account or service terminated and personal data deleted.

DATA SECURITY
-------------

We are committed to the protection of your personal data. We use TLS certificates, encryption, data access limitations, anti-virus software, and firewalls to reduce the risk of unauthorized access to personal data. No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network is entirely secure. Be mindful of security risks when you transmit personal data to us and when you post information in our public forums.

If you would like to report any security issues in any of our products, please fill out the form and required attachments and send it to [Logitech Security](https://content.logitech.com/filedrop/PSIRT).

HOW WE STORE AND PROCESS INFORMATION
------------------------------------

Data Retention
--------------

We retain personal data for as long as necessary to provide functionality and fulfill the transactions you have requested, or for other legitimate purposes such as complying with our legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our agreements. Because these needs can vary for different data types, the context of our interactions with you or your use of our Sites, actual retention periods can vary significantly.

We will retain your personal data for as long as:

* you use our products or services;
* your account is active;
* needed to provide you services;
* we are legally required to;
* to resolve disputes, and
* to enforce our agreements.

Personal data that is no longer required to be retained will be deleted at regular intervals.

Personal data collected by us may be stored and processed in the United States or in any other country we or our affiliates or service providers maintain facilities.

We take steps to ensure that the data we handle is processed as described in this Policy and according to the law wherever the data is located.

ADDITIONAL DISCLOSURES FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
-----------------------------------------------

Under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, as amended, including by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020 (together, CCPA), California residents have specific rights around Logitech's collection, use, and sharing of their personal data. We do not sell your personal data, and we will not do so in the future without providing you with notice and an opportunity to opt-out. If you require this notice in an alternative format, please email [privacy@logitech.com](mailto:privacy@logitech.com) or call our toll-free number +1 866 632 5644.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

Logitech collects and uses various types of personal data when you use its products and services, which are described within the Logitech Product and Web Privacy Policies.

Logitech shares personal data with third parties for business purposes. Specifically, here are the seven categories of activities for which we share data for business purposes:

* Auditing
* Security
* Debugging and Technical Troubleshooting
* Short term, transient use (personal data is not disclosed to third parties and it is not used to build profiles)
* Performing Services
* Internal Research
* Testing or Product/Service Improvement

If you are a resident of California, you have the right to request to know what personal data has been collected about you, how we use, share and disclose it, and to access that information. You also have the right to request that we delete your personal data, though exceptions under the CCPA may allow us to retain and use certain personal data.

We do not sell your personal data. In limited circumstances we share your personal data for advertising. You can “opt-out” of having your personal data used for this purpose by contacting us at [support.logitech.com/response-center](https://support.logitech.com/response-center).

You can learn more about how to submit a data rights request through contact details located within this policy. You may also send your request by email to [privacy@logitech.com](mailto:privacy@logitech.com) or call our toll-free number +1 866-632-5644. An agent may submit a request on your behalf, but you must provide proof that the agent is authorized to do so by providing the agent with a signed letter giving permission to submit a request on your behalf and you must confirm that authorization directly with us by sending an email to [privacy@logitech.com](mailto:privacy@logitech.com).

We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights under the CCPA. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not deny you goods or services, charge different prices or rates, or provide a different service level for exercising your privacy rights. However, we may offer certain financial incentives permitted by the CCPA that can result in different prices, discounts or quality levels. Any incentive we offer will reasonably relate to your personal data and will only be collected or processed with your consent.

California’s Shine the Light Law
--------------------------------

Separate from the CCPA, California’s Shine the Light law gives California residents the right to ask companies what personal data they share with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. We do not disclose your personal data to third parties for the purpose of directly marketing their goods or services to you unless you request it. If you have any questions regarding this policy, or would like to change your preferences, you may contact us at the address listed in this policy.

SPECIAL INFORMATION FOR EEA/UK/CH USERS
---------------------------------------

This section provides information for users in the European Economic Area (EEA), the United Kingdom (UK) and Switzerland (CH) whose personal data is processed by Logitech in the EEA, the UK or Switzerland.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

The information you provide may be transferred or accessed by Logitech entities around the world as described in this policy.

Legal bases for processing
--------------------------

We process personal data for one or more of the following reasons:

1. **To provide you with products or services you request**  
    We need to activate and register products, ensure products and services you use are working as they should, maintain products, answer questions and requests from you, and provide customer support under warranty or service contract.
2. **For Logitech’s legitimate interests**  
    We need to detect and prevent fraud and protect and defend the rights or property of other customers or third parties, or our own rights and interests. We consider your data protection interests when we do so and redact personal data as much as practicable.
3. **To meet Logitech’s legal obligations**  
    We may need to comply with EU law, EU Member State laws, UK law, Swiss law, regulatory requirements, and respond to lawful requests, court orders, and legal process.
4. **With consent**  
    Logitech uses some personal data based on consent. For example, we process usage data to conceive new products and services, and improve functionality, security and safety. We also use data with your consent for our direct marketing communications.

Your rights and choices
-----------------------

If you are a Logitech customer within the EEA, the UK or CH you may have the rights described below.

In compliance with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF) and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF), Logitech commits to resolve DPF Principles-related complaints about our collection and use of your personal data. EU and UK and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our handling of personal data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF should first contact Logitech.

To invoke your rights and resolve enquiries or complaints, please fill out [this form](https://support.logitech.com/response-center). You may also contact us via phone, email or postal mail using the contact information below:

**Phone:** +1 646-454-3200 or toll free +1 866-632-5644  
**Contact:** [privacy@logitech.com](mailto:privacy@logitech.com)  
**Postal Mail:** Logitech Privacy Office EMEA, Logitech Ireland Services Limited, City Gate Plaza Two, Mahon, Cork, Ireland  
**Data Protection Officer (DPO):** You may contact our DPO by emailing [dpo@logitech.com](mailto:dpo@logitech.com)

**Right of access and explanation**

* You can ask for an explanation of what data we have about you and how we use the data.
* You can ask for a copy of the data we have about you.

**Right of rectification**

* If you think information we have about you is inaccurate or incomplete, you can ask us to correct it.

**Right to erasure**

* You can ask us to permanently delete your data.

**Right to object**

* You can object to our use of your data on the basis of legitimate interest or for direct marketing. You can also ask not to make decisions about you based solely on automated processing. Except for direct marketing, we may continue to process your data if it’s allowed.

**Right to restriction of processing**

* You can ask us not to process your personal data if you believe the data is inaccurate, the processing is unlawful or if you need your data for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.

**Right to portability**

* You can ask to port the data you have actively or passively provided to us, where we have that data based on your consent or a contract with you and our processing of the data is automated.

**Right to complain to the supervisory authority**

* You can file a complaint about our processing of personal data with the Data Protection Commission of the Irish Supervisory Authority. Its contact information is:  
    Data Protection Commission  
    21 Fitzwilliam Square  
    Dublin 2  
    D02 RD28  
    Ireland  
    Phone: +1800 437 437, +353 (01)765 01 00  
      
    Your use of our products and services is voluntary, so where our processing is based on consent, you can withdraw your consent at any time by using the various contact information methods listed above.

In compliance with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF) and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF), Logitech commits to resolve DPF Principles-related complaints about our collection and use of your personal data. EU and UK and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our handling of personal data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF should first contact Logitech.

To invoke any of these rights and resolve enquiries or complaints, please fill out the form [support.logitech.com/response-center](https://support.logitech.com/response-center). You may also contact us via phone, email, or postal mail by using the contact information below:

**Phone:** + 1-646-454-3200 or toll free +1 866-632-5644  
**Email:** [privacy@logitech.com](mailto:privacy@logitech.com)  
**Postal Mail:** Logitech Privacy Office EMEA, Logitech Ireland Services Limited City Gate Plaza Two, Mahon, Cork, Ireland

**Data Protection Officer (DPO):** You may contact our DPO by emailing [dpo@logitech.com](mailto:dpo@logitech.com)

In compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, Logitech commits to cooperate and comply respectively with the advice of the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) and the Gibraltar Regulatory Authority (GRA) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) with regard to unresolved complaints concerning our handling of personal data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF.

You have the possibility, under certain conditions, to invoke binding arbitration for complaints regarding DPF compliance not resolved by any of the other DPF mechanisms. For additional information, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf?tabset-35584=2](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf?tabset-35584=2)

International data transfers
----------------------------

We will only transfer your personal data from the EEA, the UK and CH to countries outside these, on the basis of appropriate safeguards. When Logitech transfers data internationally we rely on i) Adequacy Decisions as adopted by European Commission on the basis of Article 45 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (GDPR and UK GDPR), ii) Standard Contractual Clauses issued by the European Commission, these are available upon request to [privacy@logitech.com](mailto:privacy@logitech.com), and iii) EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce.

Logitech and its U.S. affiliates and subsidiaries (Logitech) has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. Logitech has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/)

See below the list of Logitech U.S. affiliates and subsidiaries also adhering to the EU-U.S. DPF Principles, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles:

1. Logitech Inc.
2. Logitech Latin America Inc.

Logitech has responsibility for the processing of personal data it receives under the DPF Principles and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Logitech shall remain liable under the DPF Principles if its agent processes such personal data in a manner inconsistent with the DPF Principles, unless Logitech proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has jurisdiction over Logitech’s compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF.

Creativity and Productivity products
------------------------------------

Logitech Creativity & Productivity include hardware like mice, keyboards, touchpads, presenters, webcams, and headsets, and related software and services like Logitech Options and Options+ (Logitech Options), Logitech Capture, Logitech Presentation, Setpoint, and Logitech Control Center. We use data we collect relating to these products and services for a variety of purposes described above, including security, stability and product performance. The Privacy Policy applies to these products, but there are a few distinctions as noted below.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

Backup and Transfer of Device Settings
--------------------------------------

Logitech Options allows you to customize your mice, keyboards, and touchpads on your computer. Logitech Capture software allows you to record video and audio on your computer and change the settings of the camera. This software also offers you the ability to back up your device settings to the cloud so you can transfer those settings to other computers and set up your devices easily.

Information that may be collected includes:

* Account information like name, email address, and password to create an account or if you use a third-party open authorization (OAuth2) like Facebook or Google to log in.
* Computer information like the name, make, and model of the computer to ensure the device works correctly.
* Logitech Options specific information:  
    * Button and key customizations, including app-specific customizations
    * Other device settings like point and scroll settings of your mouse
    * Analytics data is collected subject to your consent.
* Logitech Capture specific information:
    * Scene composition and camera settings

With Logitech Options, device settings get backed up automatically. You can choose to not have your device settings backed up automatically or log out, effectively turning off the backup functionality.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

Software Updates
----------------

Our servers automatically record certain information, including the IP address, the software version, and the connected devices to check for necessary software updates and download the required device images or assets, during and after the installation of our software.

Performance, Diagnostics and Analytics
--------------------------------------

With your consent, some of our software (like Logitech Options, Capture, Presentation app, Setpoint, and Logitech Control Center) collect and record information about the software, devices, and other information such as:

* usage of software features;
* customization of your devices;
* system hardware and software like OS version;
* city-level location information using IP address;
* device usage frequency like click, and button count. For example, so that we can analyze the durability and dependability of our products, we may capture how many times each button is used during the course of 24 hours;
* Logitech Capture-specific information – we capture scene usage and camera model information. We do not analyze or transmit audio or video from the user.
* Logitech Presenters capture when you start and end a presentation, along with the application name and version you are using. We collect this information so that we can help improve functionality.

We do not collect the data you insert while using your mice, keyboards or touchpads. A Keystroke assignment refers to when you customize your device and assign a shortcut, our apps require permission from you in order to perform the assigned shortcut.

Product Functionality
---------------------

We sometimes collect data like device and application information for product features to function properly. For example, Logitech Flow is a feature in some devices that allows you to seamlessly switch between two or three computers, and transfer text, images, and files from one computer to another. To enable automatic discovery of computers during the setup process of Flow, we may collect your device identifier and IP address.

Logi AI Prompt Builder
----------------------

The Logi AI Prompt Builder is an additional feature in Options designed to facilitate your interaction with OpenAI’s ChatGPT. Logitech’s processing of personal data is limited to collecting data as described in the Performance, Diagnostics and Analytics section above.

Logitech does not share any personal data or other data with OpenAI, nor does OpenAI share any personal data or other data with Logitech.

Cameras and Products
--------------------

Logitech Circle and Mevo cameras are wireless or wired cameras with their respective software applications that can be used for a variety of purposes at home and at work. The Circle cameras provide users with rich video and audio recordings accessible from a mobile device or computer. The Mevo cameras provide users with high quality video and audio for live streaming and recording. The Privacy Policy applies to these products, but there are a few distinctions as noted below.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

Activation and Registration
---------------------------

To activate and register your products, you provide information to us to create an account, including your name, email address, password, credit card (if you subscribe to premium services), camera name, and camera settings.

We also offer activation and registration through third party open authorization (OAuth2) services, such as Facebook and YouTube so you can share clips you’ve selected and go live on that service. For this purpose, we use services such as the YouTube API Services and, as a result, you are subject to third party privacy policies such as the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [Google's security settings](https://myaccount.google.com/connections?filters=3,4&hl=en). Our apps adhere to the [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy), including the Limited Use requirements section.

While setting up the product, the country code of operation needs to be set. Some operating systems may prompt for location data access when determining the country code of operation.

Circle Video and Audio Recordings
---------------------------------

When you use Circle products and services, our servers automatically receive, record, and process data necessary to provide the service as well as information from the devices you use to view or listen to the data, including:

* video and audio recordings;
* device-specific information like hardware model, operating system version, and device identifiers such as MAC address, mobile network information, router names and meta-data concerning Apple Home Hubs and other Apple HomeKit devices;
* service event logging information;
* time and date of service use;
* on/off, and other interaction with the product;
* crashes, system activity, and hardware settings; and
* geo-location information (when location services are enabled)

Circle products may send pseudonymous information to an analytics tool, including timestamps, transmission statistics, feature usage, performance metrics, errors, etc. We use the pseudonymous information to provide, enhance, and improve our services, features, technical support and information.

Circle Features
---------------

Circle products have features that, if enabled, require us to collect and analyze data intelligently for them to work. For example, Smart Location automatically detects when you leave the house or come home, and Smart Alerts intelligently analyze motion to make sure you only get relevant alerts.

Circle Security and Storage
---------------------------

We have implemented Circle products so that no Logitech employee, contractor, vendor, affiliate, or governmental entity can access unencrypted footage. Every Circle camera has a unique private key and digital certificate, which is used to encrypt communications in transit. The Circle servers use AES 256 Bit Dual Layer Encryption to store your footage encrypted-at-rest.

Data collected is stored directly within the application, on your Device, and on servers in the U.S. or other countries where we or our affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers have facilities. We will retain collected information for as long as needed to provide the service and in accordance with the Logitech Privacy Policy.

Circle Cameras with Apple HomeKit Support
-----------------------------------------

When a Circle camera is connected to the Apple HomeKit ecosystem, Apple controls the data generated and passed to HomeKit and is responsible for the privacy and handling of your audio and video content. We have no ability or mechanism to access any HomeKit audio/video data.<.p>

If a Circle camera is only set up in HomeKit, the camera will still periodically check our servers for firmware update availability. This involves sending the model, firmware version, and the country code of operation to our servers.

If you enable the sharing of diagnostic information with Logitech through the Apple Home App, the following data will be shared with Logitech and/or Apple, and used for troubleshooting purposes only:

* device-specific information such as hardware model, names, operating system version, device identifiers such as MAC address, information about nearby wireless networks, and meta-data concerning Apple Home Hubs and other HomeKit devices;
* device event logging information;
* time and date of device use;
* on/off, and other interaction with the Product;
* crashes, system activity, hardware settings; and
* any additional details submitted by you such as descriptions, screenshots and footage.

Mevo Cameras
------------

When you use the Mevo cameras to record or go livestream, our servers automatically receive, record, and process data necessary to provide the service as well as information from the devices you use, including:

* video and audio recordings;
* device-specific information like hardware model, operating system version, firmware version, and device identifiers such as network information and IP address;
* service event logging information;
* time and date of service use;
* on/off, and other interaction with the product;
* crashes, system activity, and hardware settings; and
* geo-location information (when location services are enabled)

You may decide to use your Mevo cameras without connecting them to one of our Mevo apps, which includes the Multicam app, the Mevo Go app, the Mevo Camera app and the Mevo Webcam app.

The Mevo cameras and apps may send pseudonymous information to an analytics tool, including device information, feature usage, performance metrics, errors, etc. We use the pseudonymous information to provide, enhance, and improve our services, features, technical support and information.

If you decide to subscribe to the Mevo Pro subscription plan we will collect data necessary to provide the service as well as information from your usage, including:

* payment data;
* Streamlabs ID;
* app used for sign up; and
* statistics on usage of features.

Logitech Gaming Products
------------------------

Logitech Gaming (LogitechG) products and services include hardware like gaming keyboards, headsets, speakers, and mice, and applications for gaming consoles and PCs like G HUB software. The Privacy Policy applies to these products, but there are a few distinctions as noted below.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

Logitech G Custom Experience
----------------------------

G HUB software allows you to easily configure devices and create commands and macros for games and other applications. Adding other information about your PC, operating system, games and applications and any specific settings you adjust as part of setting up your product improves your experience. We also use this data to enhance the security and stability of our products.

If you opt-in to data analytics collection, when you use G HUB, our servers automatically receive and record information about the use of your product, including:

* location information and IP address;
* data about when you access G HUB features, such as adjusting DPI, lighting or control configuration;
* data related to the discovery of devices you connect, like a new Logitech G mouse or keyboard;
* other device and system activity including feature usage, performance metrics, errors, crash data, etc.; and
* there is a separate opt-in for submitting error logs to Logitech. If you opt in, anonymous crash related data will automatically (and manually based on user input) be sent to us for troubleshooting purposes.

Logitech G HUB Community
------------------------

When you create an account for the G HUB community, we collect information like your name, email address, country of residence, and security question responses. Accessing the G HUB community gives you access to features including:

* downloading profiles, lighting, and other settings from the Community Library;
* uploading your profiles and effects to share with the community, or for personal storage. You can remove any shared item at any time; and
* a personal profile that others in the community can view. You control what is shared in your profile.

You can unsubscribe or delete your G HUB account at any time.

Logitech G Cloud Gaming Handheld
--------------------------------

G Cloud is a handheld gaming console on which you can play cloud gaming titles and access cloud streaming services anywhere, at any time. Logitech’s processing of your personal data is limited to the Logitech hardware and the Logitech incorporated software. We collect your unique device ID for the core functioning of your console, to ensure it works correctly. There is also certain personal data collected for the core functioning that is only processed and stored locally on your console, such as your country or region for network connectivity.

If you choose to share your diagnostics and device usage data, we will receive information about your use of the console, such as your battery and charging experience, your usage of the buttons and joysticks and the audio ports. We use this information to improve our products and services.

For EEA, the UK or CH; we collect your device diagnostics and device usage data on the basis of legitimate interest. We use this information to improve our products and services. You may opt out at any time from your device settings.

Pro Alliance
------------

Pro Alliance is a website platform designed to support you as a professional gaming athlete, to improve your performance and wellness. There are services that Logitech provides for you, such as customer service support and technical product information. There are also third party service providers available that you may choose to use, such as to receive wellness coaching and services. You may be required to register with that third party, consent to their terms and review their privacy policy. We will not share your personal data with these third parties nor will we receive any of the personal data you share with those third parties.

Loupedeck
---------

Loupedeck products and services include Custom Consoles that allow you to create and edit faster. It also includes Loupedeck Marketplace, available via our website or the Loupedeck desktop app, whereby you can decide to extend the functionality of your Loupedeck Custom Console with ready-made sets of assigned functions for buttons and dials, including third party application shortcuts and third party developed add-ons.

Logitech processes certain personal data related to your console, such as your unique device ID for the core functioning of your console, to ensure it works correctly. We collect your device diagnostics and device usage data on the basis of legitimate interest. We use this information to improve our products and services.

We also process your personal data when you create an account in Loupedeck, such as your name, email address and saved custom configurations. We store this information to prevent the loss of your custom configurations.

If you are a third party developer for Loupedeck Marketplace, Logitech collects your user name and related profile information and it may be displayed to other developers and end-users in Loupedeck Marketplace.

Harmony and Related Products
----------------------------

Logitech Harmony products and services include hardware like remote controls, Harmony Hub, and Pop Button and related applications for tablets and/or smart phones like the Harmony app. The Privacy Policy applies to these products, but there are a few distinctions as noted below.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

Harmony Registration
--------------------

When you activate and register your Harmony products, we collect information like your name, email address, country of residence, and security question responses. This data is used to authenticate and associate you to your account and devices. You can also activate and register through third party open authorization (OAuth2) services, such as Facebook.

Harmony Custom Experience
-------------------------

Harmony products let you easily control and create activities or routines that combine commands from multiple devices. Adding information about your entertainment and home automation devices (like brand and model numbers), activities you choose to program (like Watch TV, Listen to Music, etc.), and any specific settings you adjust as part of setting up your product (e.g., customizing buttons) improves your experience. For example, you may actively provide your zip or postal code, your TV service provider and your preferred TV channels, shows and/or programming genres. You will know what you submit in each case, because you will manually enter the information.

We store this information to prevent the loss of your custom configurations. We also use the following information to ensure that your device works and to enhance the security and stability of our products:

* location information and IP address;
* data about when you access our software, like the features you access and when you sync your remote;
* data related to the discovery of devices in your environment, and your use of product features, like the "help" button or "reboot" actions; and
* with your consent where it’s required, information sent to an analytics tool, including feature usage, performance metrics, errors, etc.

Logitech Video Conferencing Products
------------------------------------

Logitech Video Conferencing products and services include video conferencing systems, video conferencing cameras, speakerphones, touch controllers, headsets, and webcams, as well as software like Sync, our cloud device management platform. The Privacy Policy applies to these products, but there are a few distinctions as noted below.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

Logitech Sync Service
---------------------

Logitech Sync enables users to remotely monitor and manage their Logitech video conferencing systems. Sync is made up of two parts, the desktop Sync app and the cloud “Sync Portal.” To use the Sync Portal, the Sync App must be installed on the meeting room computer. Once installed and authenticated with the Sync Portal, the Sync app will communicate directly with Sync Portal to enable remote management and monitoring capabilities.

When you create a Logitech Sync account, we collect information like your name, email address, password, country, and organization name. We use this data to authenticate and associate you to your account and devices.

Sync collects diagnostic and usage data to help maintain and improve the Sync experience. Sync collects the following information to provide management and monitoring features:

* Logitech VC product info (name, firmware version, meta data);
* Sync App version installed;
* computer info (OS type, OS version, IP, MAC address, computer specs);
* geolocation; and
* occupancy info (metadata only)

Jaybird Products and Services
-----------------------------

Jaybird products include lightweight, high-quality headphones for people with active lifestyles and related applications for tablets and/or smartphones like the Jaybird app. The Privacy Policy applies to these products, but there are a few distinctions as noted below.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

Jaybird App
-----------

The Jaybird app allows a user to:

* customize the sound of their headphones;
* update product and firmware settings;
* record the location where their headphones were last connected; and
* browse and use presets and Spotify playlists shared by other users

When you register for an account, we collect information like your name, email address, personal image (avatar), current location, and password. This data is used to authenticate and associate you to your account and devices. Jaybird also offers registration through third party open authorization (OAuth2) services, such as Facebook, Google and Spotify.

When you use your Jaybird product with the app, or the app by itself, our servers automatically receive and record certain information, including:

* product data, like your headphone model or app version;
* data about how you use the app, like the features you access and when you connect your headphones;
* data related to the discovery of devices in your environment, and your use of product features, like the “rename” action; and
* with your consent where it’s required, information sent to an analytics tool, including feature usage, performance metrics, errors, etc.

To safely back up your custom configurations, our servers receive and record additional information, including:

* current product settings, including name, button controls and voice prompt settings; and
* preset and playlist information.

Location data for Find My Buds is stored on the mobile device and is not backed up to our servers.

Ultimate Ears Products and Services
-----------------------------------

Ultimate Ears products are high quality, beautifully designed speakers and headphones. Ultimate Ears [Pro](https://pro.ultimateears.com/) and [CSX](https://custom.ultimateears.com/) both offer premium custom-fit in ear monitors (earphones). Ultimate Ears applications enable additional features and allow users to better control and customize their listening experiences. The Privacy Policy applies to these products, but there are a few distinctions as noted below.

### 

Read More

### 

Read More

Read More

Ultimate Ears Mobile Functions and Customization
------------------------------------------------

Users can customize their listening experience by configuring their devices using an Ultimate Ears application. These applications enable features like pairing multiple devices, tap controls, and multi-user DJ functionality. During the customization process, a user may be required to enter their name and contact information, including an email address and password.

We do not collect any data about the content a user plays using Ultimate Ears products.

Ultimate Ears Integration with Other Services
---------------------------------------------

Some Ultimate Ears products, like our Bluetooth speakers, can integrate with third-party services like Amazon Alexa. These integrations let users perform tasks like streaming music, ordering goods and services, and asking for information.

To enable third party services that link with your Ultimate Ears device, you may be required to register with that third party and consent to their terms. Once the link has been made, Ultimate Ears devices can receive and pass information directly to the third party.

Ultimate Ears products do not store any user command data passed from the user to the third party. Only data necessary to ensure the link between third parties and the user’s Ultimate Ears product is retained.

Custom In Ear Monitors (IEM)
----------------------------

Ultimate Ears [Pro](https://pro.ultimateears.com/) and [CSX](https://custom.ultimateears.com/) offer premium custom-fit in ear monitors (earphones). Most Pro devices require user ear impressions, which are typically created digitally or with molds. by a third party, most commonly an audiologist. The CSX devices require images and impressions of the user's ear to optimize the product fit. We retain these impressions in case of loss, reordering, or reproduction, or until a user requests that they be discarded.

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY
----------------------

We will occasionally update this Policy. If we make significant changes to this Policy, or in how we will use your personal data, we will notify you through appropriate channels, such as posting a notice on our website or sending you a direct communication.

We will not make any changes that are less protective of your personal data collected in the past without your consent.

We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

Thank you for your interest in Logitech and our products and services.

About
-----

About

Values
------

Values

Partners
--------

Partners

CUSTOMERS
---------

CUSTOMERS

 I want personalized marketing from Logitech. You can unsubscribe anytime. See our [privacy policy](https://www.logitech.com/legal/web-privacy-policy.html).

Thank you. Your subscription is successful

©2024 Logitech. All rights reserved

Cart
----

Loading...

Item Subtotal: (Not Including Tax or Shipping)

Enter Promo Code

Promo Code  Apply

msg

flash

By checking this box, I agree to the [Privacy Policy](https://store.digitalriver.com/store/defaults/en_US/DisplayDRPrivacyPolicyPage/eCommerceProvider.DR+globalTech+Inc.) and the [Terms of Sale](https://store.digitalriver.com/store/defaults/en_US/DisplayDRTermsAndConditionsPage/eCommerceProvider.DR+globalTech+Inc.) of [DR globalTech Inc.](https://store.digitalriver.com/store/defaults/en_US/DisplayDRAboutDigitalRiverPage/eCommerceProvider.DR+globalTech+Inc.) See our [Privacy Policy](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/legal/privacy-policy.html) .

Or

Checkout with ESW: Clicking "Checkout" takes you to the ESW checkout, where payment is made and your order is processed by ESW, Logitech's partner for international sales.

Your cart is currently empty. Begin shopping now Close

### NOTIFY ME

We'll email you when this product becomes available for purchase

SUBMIT

#### Get the latest from Logitech

I want personalized marketing from Logitech. You can unsubscribe anytime. See our [privacy policy](https://www.logitech.com/en-us/legal/web-privacy-policy.html)

### Success!

Thank you for signing up.
